fxmarketleaders.com 2019-05-29

# Privacy Policy - FX Leaders

[Home](https://www.fxleaders.com/) / Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important. We have created this Privacy Policy so you can understand your rights as an FX Leaders website user.  We may intermittently make changes to the policy. The changes will be included on this page.  It is up to you to review this Privacy Policy regularly and stay informed about any changes made to it. We encourage you to visit this page often. ** ** By using the website you agree to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy and terms of use. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier versions.

 **Collection of your email address**  
Signing up for the website requires you to supply an email address, or other information needed to contact you online. Any email address supplied may later be accessed, updated, modified and deleted. Please note, we may keep a copy of any previous email addresses for our records.

The email address you provide will be used to send you daily newsletters and market updates and will not be used for commercial purposes or sold to third-parties.

This information is used to aid and improve your use of the website, for communication purposes, and to comply with any requirements of the law. We shall also use this information to respond to any questions you might have. Without your consent, your email address will not be sold or revealed to third parties, other than as specified in this Privacy Policy. unless we are legally obliged to do so (for example, if requested to do so by Court Order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or any other crime).

If necessary, we may disclose your information to protect our legal rights. For example, if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful actions, or we have good reason to believe that disclosing information is necessary in order to conform to the requirements of the law or comply with governmental orders, court orders, or legal process served on us; or to protect and defend our property or other rights, the users of the website or the public.  This includes the exchange of information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk protection.  If the website ever files for bankruptcy, is part of a reorganization, sells its assets or merges with a separate company, we may sell information provided to us through the website to a third party or share your information with the third party or company we merge with.

Links to third party websites may be present on this website. Even if the websites are accessed via links from our website, we are not responsible for their privacy practices or the content. Use of these third-party websites is done entirely at your own risk. It is recommended that you check the privacy and security policies of every website you visit. Clicking on a third party link essentially takes you to a third party’s website.  We make no representation or warranty as to the effectiveness, quality, legitimacy or data protections of any third party website.

If at any time you would like FX Leaders to delete your personal information from the database send an email to support@fxleaders.com and your details will be deleted within 72 hours.

 **Cookies**

FX Leaders uses cookies on our website to remember your log-in details. In addition, we use third-party cookies like [Google analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy) to learn how users behave on the website, and, use [MailChimp](https://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/) for our email correspondence. All of the information collected is aggregated and anonymous and is only used to improve the efficiency of the website. The cookies we use do not store individual or personal information and cannot track your browsing activity.
